Do we even have a CIA? Um, so what I
mean by that is the CIA uh seems to let
Israel run wild inside this country. And
so espionage to no end stole our nuclear
secrets, our uranium, our nuclear
triggers, all of our top secrets. And
yet we're like, "Oh, they're our best
allies." And we let them run. And and in
fact, one more, you know, Epstein was
part of uh Iran Contra. And so it's not
like the CIA is not aware of what's
happening here. And so does it exist or
is it just simply the MSAD?
>> You know, it's it's changed a lot over
the years in that when I first joined
the CIA, we did not like the Israelis at
all.
>> Joining us now is John Kuryaku. He's a
former CIA officer and a whistleblower
uh who uh uh uh blew the whistle on
torture uh that we were doing inside the
government and has won several awards
including counterterrorism service medal
meritorious honor award, CIA exceptional
performance award, CIA sustained
superior performance award and has a
number of books out. John, welcome to
the show.
>> Thank you so much Shank. You know, you
and I have never had a chance to
actually meet, and you did me a solid
many years ago by talking about my very
first smuggled out letter from prison.
You read it on the air, and I've always
been very appreciative. That's
interesting. Okay, so I saw Look, we're
going to get into super important things
about like who does the CIA actually
work for. Uh but first, I saw a clip
where you said that I had uh railed
against you. Do you know where that came
from? Because that never happened. Hold
on, pause because I set this up. Okay, I
came across the clip and I was like,
"Oh, no." But I like John Kuryaku a lot.
Like, what's the beef? So, this is the
clip.
>> What was it?
>> Ed. Okay, this is the moment. Take a
look.
>> Hassan Piker's mother mother's maiden
name is Weaguer. And I wondered if he
was related to Chank Wager. Michael
Gardner's telling us that he's Czech
Waguer's nephew. It's funny. Chank Wager
has never really been a friend of mine
either. The second thing I ever did that
got wide press coverage after blowing
the whistle um it was my it was my open
letter to uh to my supporters from
prison that became my first letter from
Lorettto. That's when Jake Tapper came
to uh to the prison to interview me. Uh
the the the response was universally
positive and interested except for Chank
Wiger.
Chen Weaguer just for 30 minutes just
ripped me and I never understood that
because back then, you know, I I
probably agreed on 95% of the issues
with Chen Weaguer. Like, why is he
attacking me like this? But it's just
his
>> I I've never been able to draw a bead on
on Chen Weaguer. I mean, I wanted to I I
kind of felt like I should have been
friends with him. He's one of those
guys. It's like an unrequited bromance
where you're sort of like you reach out,
you're like, "We should be buds. We
agree about a lot of stuff and then you
know they never call, they never write.
>> Well, it could be quieted now. So, John,
what in the world was that?
>> I don't know.
>> No, it was a mistaken identity thing
because I became obsessed with figuring
out what it was and I went through our
archives and no such thing exists. So,
it must have been a mistake ident.
Yeah, I I I want to apologize for that
because I think I must have been
temporarily insane or something. That
had to be that's what I'm going with.
>> Yeah. Yeah. No, no, don't sweat it. The
mistaken identity, no big deal. Okay,
let's get to serious stuff. So, look,
John, the main thing that I've been
wanting to ask you for a long time is,
do we even have a CIA? Um, so what I
mean by that is the CIA uh seems to let
Israel run wild inside this country. And
so espionage to no end stole our nuclear
secrets, our uranium, our nuclear
triggers, all of our top secrets. And
yet we're like, "Oh, they're our best
allies and we let them run." And and in
fact, one more, you know, Epstein was
part of uh Iran Contra. And so it's not
like the CIA is not aware of what's
happening here. And so does it exist or
is it just simply the MSAD?
>> You know, it's it's changed a lot over
the years in that when I first joined
the CIA, we did not like the Israelis at
all. They were spying on us. They made
it clear. They openly spied on us. They
would bring us gifts that had listening
devices embedded in them to the point
where they were not allowed in the
building. We had to rent space to do our
liaison meetings with them because they
just simply were not permitted to come
into the headquarters building. Well,
that that was what 35 years ago. And now
all of a sudden they're being like
embedded with the CIA that there's a
provision in the National Defense
Authorization Act for 2027 that
colllocates them with the the Pentagon
and then allows even closer like five
eyes style liaison with um with the CIA.
And then at the same time, just two
weeks ago, NBC News reported that the
director of DIA, the Defense
Intelligence Agency, had to send out an
all hands email saying that the Israelis
are being unusually aggressive right now
in trying to recruit assets inside DIA
that all DIA employees need to be extra
careful. So, what are we doing here?
Either either the Israelis are ranked as
critical threat for counter
intelligence, which is what they were
when I was there along with the
Russians, the Chinese, the Cubans, and
the North Koreans,
or we're joined at the hip. But it can't
be both.
>> So, here's my follow-up question for for
you on everything that you just said.
What changed? Is it blackmail? like how
did our government and and not just the
CIA, how did our government go from
understanding the risks of being
associated with the Israelis,
understanding that they spy on us,
understanding that while we may say that
they're our allies, in reality they act
like they're our adversaries. So,
>> what changed?
>> Do they have dirt on powerful people in
our government? Or I mean, I'm asking
you to speculate or maybe you know
something we don't know.
>> Yeah. No, they they probably do, but I
think it's I think it's broader and more
nefarious than that in that this is
really a political change. You know, the
the last any Arab leader will tell you
and and many have told me or I've been
in the room when they've told the
American ambassador, the last American
president to give the Arabs a fair shake
was George HW Bush. The last one. They
loved George HW Bush. They loved
Kennedy. And they loved Eisenhower. and
everybody else has been a Zionist in
terms of policy. Well, we've had a
string of Zionist presidents and they
just keep the the Israelis keep chipping
away little by little by little, not
just in the White House, but on Capitol
Hill through Apac and they've gotten us
to the point where if you disagree not
just with Israeli policy, if you
disagree with Benjamin Netanyahu as a
person, you are labeled as anti-Semitic.
of course took decades to get to that
point but they did it.
>> Yeah. So John more follow-ups here. So
first of all on your point about
disagree with Netanyahu uh only a third
of Jewish Americans agree with
Netanyahu. Twothirds are against them.
So apparently twothirds of Jews in
America are anti-Semitic by this
ludicrous definition. Ludicrous. And
it's obvious. Can
>> I add something to that?
>> Yeah. because of the party system in uh
in Israel, Benjamin Netanyahu has never
won more than 27% of the vote in Israel.
So, are we supposed to assume then that
73% of Israelis are anti-Semitic?
>> Yeah,
>> it's outrageous.
>> Uh yes, and I could list other uh
historic leaders that did not win a
majority, but one around that number and
then went on to do great damage. Uh so,
okay. Now, our press uh I believe is
mainly is Israeli propaganda. Why do I
say that? Because they keep telling us
that things are normal. So, I just want
to do a quick checklist with you to see
if these things are normal. So, [snorts]
>> they keep saying, "Oh, your our allies
doing espionage to the point where they
are stealing our the most sensitive
technology and intelligence and using it
to build weapons of mass destruction and
doing it over and over and over again is
perfectly normal. Is that really
normal?" No, of course not. And if it
was any other country in the world, we
would be on the brink of war with them
right now.
>> I mean, forget allies, we'd be on the
brink of war with them. Okay. So then
number two, they say, "Oh, to merge our
militaries, as you're talking about
section 219 and the technology and so
that they could take one now soon to be
$1.5 trillion of money we're spending on
defense and they get the entire benefit
of that for free." They say that's all
perfectly normal. We constantly are
merging our militaries with allies. Is
that normal?
>> We're merging our militaries with the
closest allies that we have in the
world. Very specifically the British,
the Canadians, the Australians, and the
New Zealanders. You know, we've got good
relations with the rest of the the
members of NATO, as one example. Israel
is not in NATO. We have close relations
with most European Union countries.
Israel is not a member of the European
Union. And then just a couple of weeks
ago, the Israeli defense minister said
publicly in a in an interview that
Israel's next war would be against
Turkey. Well, guess what? Turkeykey's a
member of NATO. And if there were to be
hostilities between Israel and Turkey,
and Turkey invoked Article 5 of the of
the NATO charter, an attack on one is an
attack on all. the United States would
have to go to war with Israel to defend
Turkey. Is the United States going to go
to war with Israel? Of course not. And
so what happens? The Israelis then
successfully destroy NATO. Is that
really the the road we want to go down?
>> Not normal. Last one. Last one. Go. Go
ahead. Yeah. So, uh, dozens of Israeli
spies were arrested after 9/11. I'm not
asking about why they were arrested or
what they did, but they were arrested
and they were definitively Israeli
spies. And then we just let them go
free. Yes. Is that normal?
>> Yes,
>> that actually is normal. Um nor normal
normally if let's say an American spy
gets caught in a friendly country, you
know, publicly we deny deny deny that
this person is a spy. We deny and then
secretly quietly we go to the the
station chief will go to the head of the
service and say, "Listen, he's my guy.
You busted us. Do me a favor here and
just let him go." and then quietly
they'll let him go. They may make him
cool his heels for a week or two, but
eventually they're going to let him go.
The reason why I I'm speculating here. I
believe that the reason why there were
so many Israeli spies arrested in New
York in the days after 9/11 is that the
Israelis had advanced warning of 9/11
and didn't tell us. And that was a
policy decision. We asked every ally in
the world. We begged them if they had
any sources inside al-Qaeda, please help
us because we knew this massive attack
was coming, but we didn't know when and
where. We knew it was going to be giant.
We just didn't know when and where. I
believe that the Israelis did know that
they had infiltrated al-Qaeda, but they
didn't tell us because they wanted us to
attack al-Qaeda. They knew that if we
were attacked that we would overreact
like we did. We would launch a war that
lasted 20 years. We would kill 2 million
Muslims, which we did, and spend
something like $6 something trillion
dollar on national defense. You know,
just like they knew chaos in Iraq was
good for Israel, chaos in Libya was good
for Israel, chaos in Syria was good for
Israel, and now chaos in Iran is good
for Israel. It hasn't changed since
9/11.
>> Cancer on our globe. Honestly, I it's
So, you just said something very
provocative. Uh something that I alluded
to in one post on X once, and I didn't
even allude to it as aggressively as you
just did. I just noted the, you know,
five Israelis who got arrested because
they were seen celebrating the World
Trade Center getting attacked. Um, and I
was like, whatever happened with this?
Like, what is this? And there is
evidence that the Israelis had
fornowledge. So, can you can you get
into that a little bit because I think
it's important for members of our
audience who might not know what that
evidence is and why so many people um
have believed that the Israelis had
fornowledge.
>> Yeah. Dozens of Israelis were were
Israeli citizens were arrested uh by
NYPD officers on September 11th and in
the days after September 11th, mostly
for photography, for taking pictures of
sensitive sites, taking pictures of the
uh World Trade Center, things like that,
or making comments uh about the the
attacks. And so they were picked up and
they were held on suspicion of, you
know, something national security
related. And finally the Israelis came
to us and said, "Listen, these are our
guys. Just let them go." Right? They're
they're worried about you. They were
worried about the World Trade Center.
They didn't mean any harm. I think they
were there just to sort of document what
was happening because they knew it was
going to happen. Um,
in in the months before 9/11
>> Mhm.
>> I I was working in the CIA's
counterterrorism center at the time and
um in the months before 9/11, the
leadership of the counterterrorism
center was scrambling. Uh I happened to
be entertaining a group of Middle
Eastern intelligence officers one day.
It was July the 6th, 2001, and Kofheer
Black, the director of the
counterterrorism center, came into my my
meeting, shocked me. I jumped up at
attention and I said, "Oh, gentlemen,
this is Kofer Black. He's the director
of the CIA's counterterrorism center."
And Kov minced no words. He said,
"Something terrible is going to happen.
We don't know what. We don't know where.
We don't know when, but we know it's
going to be an attack on a massive
scale. And he went into some detail with
them. And [clears throat] he said at the
end of his little talk, I'm begging you.
He said, if you have any sources inside
al-Qaeda, please help us. Well, the
truth was we didn't have any sources
inside al-Qaeda. And that's why we
needed help from liaison. But they
didn't. The other Arab countries didn't.
The Gulf countries didn't. The
Pakistanis either didn't or wouldn't
tell us. And the Israelis just sat back
and waited for it all to happen and then
came and said, "We are one with you,
America. We are with you." Well, they
knew exactly what was going to happen.
Yeah.
>> And then 8 years later, uh, under Obama,
we began arming al-Qaeda terrorists in
Syria. [clears throat]
>> That's exactly right.
>> Yeah,
>> that's exactly right. So, John, I just
want to ask one more followup about that
because uh so I call this oops, it got
past the goalie, right? So, and and
I like of course our press never talks
about it. They all pretended everything
is a conspiracy theory. Uh I believe
that the phrase conspiracy theory was
actually concocted after the Kennedy
shooting to just call everything that
was that against the official government
position a crazy lunatic thing to
believe. uh etc. But okay, so but I
could never square well you know if
there was a conspiracy and there was did
they really kill all the people on the
planes and how did they get the Arabs to
do the thing that they wanted blah blah
blah and then uh many many many years
later uh in fact after October 7th I
realized oh you know this is actually
potentially easier than I realized you
just find plots and you probably in
intelligence and that's why I'm asking
you find plots all the time and if you
want one of them to be successful for
political reasons. You go, "Oh, I just
got past the goalie. There's nothing I
could do." So, is [clears throat] it
possible that October 7th was another
one of those?
>> Oh, listen. Call me a conspiracy
theorist, but I think that's exactly
what happened. We know now in retrospect
that for two weeks before October 7th,
Israelis who were living in settlements
along the the line the border with Gaza
were reporting back to uh the Ministry
of uh national security that something
was happening in Gaza. And Idomar
Bengavir said no nothing is happening in
Gaza. The next attack is going to be in
the West Bank. And it was Idomar
Bengavir who ordered that government um
uh what's the word I want to use that
that assets were being used government
assets were being used against you know
possible cells in the West Bank. Well,
there was nothing happening in the West
Bank and
>> and these settlers were saying look you
know the the Gaza Palestinians are
flying kites along the border. They're
releasing balloons. They're checking
wind speeds. their their chatter uh on
the walkietalkies.
No, you're wrong. It's going to be in
the West Bank. So, I think boy, I really
like that, you know, slip by the goalie.
I think I might steal that because I
think that is exactly what happened.
>> Yeah. I mean, and the fact that it took
six hours for the IDF to respond. And
you know, just fast forwarding to the
moment that we're in now, I just can't
get over the incredibly weak and
pathetic arguments that are being made
by individuals who have been corrupted
with money from the Israel lobby,
essentially arguing that we must merge
our militaries because the IDF, I mean,
how could we give up this opportunity uh
to take advantage of their expertise and
their superior operations? They took six
hours to respond to October 7th
>> and then killed the Israelis
>> and then killed their own. Exactly.
>> that were in cars trying to evacuate the
area. Yeah. You know, one one thing that
that most mainstream outlets don't talk
about is that the Israelis are already
in the United States training local
police departments. We know, for
example, that the Israelis are training
the Atlanta police. that this area now
called Cop City is the site of Israeli
police and Israeli IDF training our own
police. I don't want the Israelis
training American police departments.
The Israelis have no respect for human
rights or civil rights or civil
liberties. And so, look, this is a
country that has that has bombed seven
of its neighbors in the past year.
>> Is that really the country that we want
to throw our lot in with? I would say
no.
>> So, John, uh, Pete Hexath wrote in his
book that the IDF should be in American
streets. So, there's so many Israeli
assets inside our, uh, government that
it's unbelievable. So, okay, which
brings me back to section 219. So, you
mentioned it earlier, used to be called
section 224, now it's 219 going into the
National Defense Authorization Act. They
tried it with no vote before. Now,
there's more of a, you know, uprising
against it. Of course, as usual, Roana,
Tom Massie leading the charge against it
and as usual, uh, 94% of Congress
saying, "No, no, no. We serve Israel
loyally." So, tell tell us about the
dangers of merging our technology with
with Israel's and why this should be
completely unacceptable to the American
people.
>> You know what, Chank? I'll start I'll
start back from my very first week in
the CIA, January of 1990. uh that first
week you just sit in the auditorium and
you get briefing after briefing after
briefing from you know the director
comes and congratulates you. Then you
hear from the head of HR and the head of
health insurance and the head of life
insurance and the director of security
and the director of security gave us a
couple of you know kind of real life
day-to-day pointers. don't ever eat in
this steakhouse down the street from the
CIA because the KGB thinks we all eat
there and every table is taken by the
KGB, for example. I've never been in
there. But another thing he said, um,
and this is dated, it's 1990, but I
would venture to say that it's worse
today than it was in 1990. He said that
there were two official Israeli
intelligence representatives in
Washington. This was at the Israeli
embassy in Washington. It was uh one
person from Mossad and one person from
Shinbet. Okay. And they carry out
liaison. But the FBI was able to
identify
187 Israeli spies spread out all across
America,
mostly infiltrating American defense
contractors to steal our secrets. It
didn't end with the arrest of Jonathan
Pard. and he said Israel is critical
threat for counter intelligence along
with Russia, China, Cuba and North
Korea. And I think Iran may have been on
the list at the time too. Um, and
Israel. And I'll give you another
example. When we came up with this
ill-advised F-35,
the Israelis came to us first and said,
"We want the F-35." And we said, "Great.
We're going to give you the F35. We're
going to slightly degrade the avionics
because, god forbid one gets shot down
and the Russians or the Chinese, you
know, get it in Syria or Iran or
whatever. So, we're going to call the
F-35I. I I for Israel. The Israelis
said, "No, we want your F-35. We don't
want any I with degraded avionics." At
the same time, the Emiratis came to us
and they said, "We want this new F-35."
And we said, "Great. will give you the
F-35 with slightly degraded avionics
because god forbid one should be shot
down and the Russians and the Chinese,
the Iranians get it. We're going to call
it the F-35E for Emirates. The Emirates
gladly took the F-35E.
The Israelis sent their spies all over
the defense sector to steal the avionics
so that when they finally got the F-35i,
they could upgrade them on their own.
And that's the country that we want side
by side with our people in the Pentagon
and the CIA and god forbid NSA or DIA
when the director of DIA is warning
every single employee that they are
unusually aggressive against us right
now, the Israeli Mossad.
>> Yeah.
>> And that people have to be extra
careful. So that brings me back to the
what we started with, John, which is I I
is the CIA still American. Uh because
they don't act like it. And and so all
this espionage is going on. It's super
obvious that it's the Israelis. And it
doesn't seem like we're doing a damn
thing about it. We're just letting them
run wild in this country. And I want to
go back to to Epstein because [snorts]
we know that Epstein was part of Iran
Contra. He helped clean out the planes
that the CIA was using and he did that
with Lex Wexner and seemingly with
Mossad and let let's let you know I'll
let you talk about what you know how
much you know about that right but but
also okay so the CIA at that moment
knows Epstein seems to be with Israeli
intelligence because we just did a deal
with him. We just did a deal with him.
Then they let Epstein rape girls in this
country for decades afterwards. So, is
the CIA working for America or for
Israel?
>> You know, I hate to say this, but I the
only conclusion that I can draw is that
it's working for Israel. You know, when
you've got the likes of Mike Pompeo at
the CIA, who was one of the the foremost
Zionists on Capitol Hill. Um, and he and
he's guiding policy. Remember, the CIA
is a policy support organization. It's
not a policy organization. It's supposed
to do what the president tells it to do.
But historically, it had pushed back
against Israel. And then you get Mike
Pompeo in there, who might as well be
the head of Mossad for for his uh
support of Israel, everything begins to
change. And when and when you have this
constant pressure from Capitol Hill
where practically everybody is taking
money from Apac
and um and and are they're primared if
they don't take money from Apac or if
they don't tow the line that Apac sets
then you know you lose that independence
and the next thing you know you are
working for the Israelis. Oh
>> god. So how do you see this ending?
because we don't live in a sovereign
country. Under what you just described,
we don't live in a sovereign country and
um it fills me with rage and I imagine
it fills a lot of Americans with rage.
So, how does this come to an end?
Because eventually American citizens are
going to have enough of this.
>> Yeah.
>> Um so, how do you see this playing out?
>> In one of two ways really. On the one
hand, I I've long been accused of being
irrationally optimistic about life, and
the the optimist in me says, "Well,
certainly our elected leaders will come
to their senses eventually."
>> But I've got to be realistic. And I I
just don't think that's going to happen.
>> I don't think that they'll come to their
senses because well, for a couple of
reasons. Number one, because if you look
at the incremental change over the LA or
changes over the last 35 years, every
one of those changes has been in support
of Israel. Yep.
>> Number one. Number two,
even though public opinion polls are
showing that now a clear majority of
Americans uh believe that our
relationship with Israel is too close,
believe that Israel is committing a
genocide in in Gaza, believe that Israel
is the aggressor uh in in all of these
recent conflicts, our elected officials
still line right up in support of
Israel. And you've got people like
Thomas Massie and Ro Kana and a small
handful of others, Marjorie Taylor Green
who's now gone, but a small number
willing to stand up, that number doesn't
really grow. So even if let's say 77% of
Democrats pled say they support the
Palestinian side in this conflict,
90% of elected Democrats support the
Israelis. And where does that leave us?
That leaves us in a place where we don't
have a democracy.
>> Yeah, we are an occupied country. So,
okay, I now have a random question for
you that I've been meaning to ask for a
long time. So, I want to make sure I get
it in here. So, uh Barack Obama did
something unacceptable uh when he bombed
Anoir Alvaki. Uh he he went outside of
the judiciary and he said due process
does not have to be judicial process.
the executive branch can just decide to
execute an American citizen. Uh, and
they did, but that was already egregious
enough, but they say coincidentally in a
second and completely different bombing,
they also killed Alby's 16-year-old son.
And then [clears throat]
coincidentally, in a third bombing, they
killed his 8-year-old daughter. So, were
those coincidences or I have a theory on
this one and I'm curious what you think
that maybe Anoir Albakuyu was working
with the CIA but then he flipped on him
and so he knew things that the CIA
didn't want out and so they were wanted
to cover all their bases on anyone who
might have known.
>> I think that's entirely plausible. I'll
tell you, I was one of a very small
handful of CIA officers who had actually
met Anoir Alaki. I met him when he was
the imam of the of the mosque in false
church, Virginia. My Arabic teacher, uh
CIA employee, Arabic teacher took us
there uh so we could learn some of the
uh the vocabulary words associated with
Islam. and um he gave us a tour of the
mosque. He took us to the uh Arabic
language bookstore and then we went to
lunch with him. In 2011, I went to Yemen
to do a study. I was the senior
investigator on the Senate Foreign
Relations Committee at the time working
for John Kerry. And I went to Yemen and
my first meeting on that trip was with
the uh the legal attaches, the FBI
representative in the American embassy.
And I made a joke about, you know, what
are you doing? I'm sitting here in your
office. You should be out looking for
Anoir Alaki.
And he said, "We know where Anoir Alaki
is within 3 ft 24 hours a day." And I
stupidly said, "So why don't you arrest
him?"
>> Mhm.
>> Well, because there was never any
intention of of arresting him.
>> The intent was to to kill him, to track
him, and to kill him. That was a policy
decision that was made. But why did we
let him
go as far as he did? I think you're on
to something here. I think he was
probably a CIA asset at one time.
Remember, he was an American citizen. He
was born in Albuquerque, New Mexico. His
father was the Yemen Ambassador to the
United States at the time and and then
went on to become the Yemen Minister of
Agriculture. And um and I think that he
self-radicalized after a while and they
just decided to take him out
at a time and place of their choosing.
May I add one other thing, Jack? You
raised something that's very important.
It's something I've been yelling about
for years.
We murdered him without ever charging
him with a crime. He had a
constitutional right to face his
accusers in a court of law and to be
judged by a jury of his peers. And we
murdered him in cold blood. He had never
been charged with a crime. But then a
week later, we murdered his 16-year-old
son and 16-year-old nephew as they sat
at a cafe drinking tea. They were
children and they had never been charged
with any crime. And then we murdered his
daughter just for good measure, an
8-year-old, which made Obama a child
killer. Of course, he already was a
child killer, but made him a child
killer again. And nobody really seems to
care. What about his rights? Because
remember what Eric Holder told Ran Paul.
If the president wants to kill you, he's
perfectly within his legal rights to
kill you. And it doesn't matter if you
have never been charged with a crime. If
the president of the United States
doesn't like your politics,
he can make you vapor
with a missile.
>> Yeah.
>> We're in super dark times here. Uh I'm
going to So we got to go. But John, uh,
am I right that your background is Greek
originally?
>> Yes, sir.
>> Okay. But I want to end, you know, you
say you're an optimist. I'm an optimist.
Uh, the one beautiful thing about this
country is here's a Turk, a Greek, and
an Armenian. All fighting, [laughter]
>> right?
>> And by the way, this is really
important. All
>> John, I got your back. [laughter]
all all Americans and all fighting not
for Turkey, Greece or Armenia, but for
America as it's supposed to be. And and
so,
>> you know, we we love this country and we
want its sovereignty and its freedom
back. So, thank you for joining us,
John. Really appreciate it.
>> Thank you so much for the invitation. It
was a pleasure.
>> Come back soon.
>> I look forward to it.
>> Every time you ring the bell below, an
angel gets his wings. Totally not true,
but it does keep you updated on our live
shows.